## Eric Kim

1151 Windsor Mews Coquitlam , BC Canada V3B 0M9 778 838 4547 gimtaelin0701@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Worked as a cashier at Chicko Chicken, ensuring order accuracy while thriving in a fast-paced environment and multitasking. Assisted kitchen staff with food preparation and packaging. Additionally, as a Day Camp Leader, provided team support and managed safety, demonstrating strong leadership and communication skills.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Chicko Chicken, Coquitlam, BC Canada

08/2024 - 12/2024

Casher & Kitchen Assistant

- Greeted customers, took orders accurately, and processed payments using POS system, ensuring a smooth checkout experience.
- Assisted customers with menu selections, and ensured all orders were correct and delivered on time.
- Managed cash, credit, and mobile payments, maintaining accuracy in transactions and giving the correct change.
- Assisted kitchen staff with food prep.

### Coquitlam Recreation Centre, Coquitlam, BC Canada

07/2022 - 09/2022

Summer Day Camp Leader

- Led and supervised a group of children under 10 years old, ensuring their safety, and well-being throughout the camp day.
- Monitored children at all times, both indoors and outdoors, ensuring they followed camp rules and stayed safe during play and activities. Responded swiftly to any accidents or incidents.
- Worked alongside fellow camp leaders and staff to coordinate group activities.

### **EDUCATION**

### Simon Fraser University

2023 - Present

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

### **SKILLS**

- Order accuracy
- Customer service
- Multi-tasking
- Kitchen staff support
- Online orders preparation